thenibble.com 2018-12-01

# Gourmet Food - THE NIBBLE - Great Food Finds™ - Privacy Policy

### _Home_

## Privacy Policy 

**Effective date February 1, 2005**

THE NIBBLE™ and its website, TheNibble.com, and newsletter are products of Lifestyle Direct, Inc. 

This policy does not cover information collected from you on sites linked to or from TheNibble.com.  

It is the goal of THE NIBBLE™ website and newsletter to bring you information that is tailored to your individual needs and, at the same time, protect your privacy. A summary of the various ways we treat the information you may provide us with follows: 

**I. The Type of Information We Collect**

**Personal Information**

You will always know when we are collecting personal information, because we only collect personal information with your knowledge and consent, when you voluntarily submit it to us through our online forms and questionnaires.  For instance, when you subscribe to our newsletter, enter a sweepstakes or contest, complete a survey or poll, send us feedback, request additional information, etc., you are asked to provide information such as your e-mail address, name or phone number. Optional information such as your gender, age group, and/or household income range, or mailing address also may be requested. 

**Use of Site By Minors**

TheNibble.com is not intended for use by children, especially those under age 18, due to the discussion of wine, beer, and other alcoholic beverages. By law, no one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information. Minors between the ages of 13 and 17 must get the permission of their parent(s) or legal guardian(s) before making any purchases on this site.

**Non-Personal Information**

When you use our websites, we may also collect information that, by itself, cannot be used to identify or contact you. This includes demographic information (age, gender, income, education, profession, zip code, etc.). Non-personal information may also include technical information, such as your IP address, the type of browser you are using, the websites you visit immediately before and immediately after you visit our websites, and other anonymous data involving your use of our websites. 

**Cookies**

We use “cookies” to enhance your visits to our websites. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies do not store personal information about you, unless you knowingly provide it on the website. Cookies can store non-personal information, such as what websites, pages, or advertisements your browser has accessed. Cookies are not harmful to you or your computer: they cannot in any way relay any data you have on your personal computer to us.

We use cookies to store information and personalize your experience on TheNibble.com. For example, cookies allow our websites to recognize your browser as a returning visitor, and thus save and remember any preferences that may have been set while you were previously browsing the site. We may use them to deliver tailored editorial content and advertising. Some of our advertisers might occasionally serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers.

You do have control over cookies. Most browsers can be set to notify you when a cookie is being placed on your computer. They also can be set to refuse to accept cookies, although this may limit your Internet experience.

**II. How We Use The Information You Provide**

**Personal Information**

THE NIBBLE™ uses your personal information to provide you with the service you have requested. For example, if you want our newsletter, we use your e-mail address to send it to you. If you enter an online sweepstakes or contest, we will use your email information to notify you if you are a winner, and your phone number as a back-up in case the email bounces back or you do not respond. We may also use your e-mail to communicate with you about new features, products or services. 

TheNibble.com does not give or sell your e-mail address unless you request us to do so. If you have completed a Subscriber Profile, you have the option to check a box or boxes that allows us to provide your e-mail address and/or other information you select with our partners, and with carefully selected companies we think offer products and services that may be of interest to you. If you do not check those boxes, your information will not be shared. 

If you do check the boxes, you can uncheck them at any time. If you opt out, we will make reasonable efforts to discontinue the particular communications as soon as possible. Understand that due to communications already in the queue, you may still receive communications for a few weeks.  If you are opting out of partner or third party communications, it can take 90-120 days for communications to cease. 

We may also provide your information to our advertisers, so that they can serve ads to you that meet your needs or match your interests. While THE NIBBLE™ will seek to require such third parties to follow appropriate privacy policies and will not authorize them to use this information except for the express purpose for which it is provided, TheNibble.com does not bear any responsibility for any actions or policies of third parties. 

There may also be occasion when we are legally required to provide access to our database in order to cooperate with police investigations or other legal proceedings. In those instances, the information is provided only for that purpose. 

**Email Communications and Online Suggestion Forms**

If you send us an e-mail with questions or comments, or use one of our online suggestion and feedback forms, we may use your personal information to respond to your questions or comments, and we may save your questions or comments for future reference. However, aside from any reply to your communication, we will not add your information to any mailing list or database.

In order for you to receive other, general, communications from THE NIBBLE™, you must go to Subscriber Preferences and fill out a profile indicating your interests. There, you have the option to opt in and opt out of a variety of communications.

**Non-Personal Information**

While your individual information is protected as outlined above, we reserve the right to use aggregated, anonymous data about our users as a group for any business purpose, such as analyzing usage trends and seeking compatible advertisers and partners. 

**III. Disclosure of Your Information To Third Parties**

**Personal Information**

We occasionally offer promotions like sweepstakes or free product offers in conjunction with a third party sponsor. If you choose to participate in one of those promotions, we will share your information with the sponsor if they need it to send you a product or other special promotion they offer.

We may disclose personal information when we are required or requested to do so by law, court order or other government or law enforcement authority or regulatory agency; to enforce or apply our rights and agreements; or when we believe in good faith that disclosing this information is necessary or advisable, including, for example, to protect the rights, property, or safety of THE NIBBLE™, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**Non-Personal Information**

We may use third-party advertising companies to deliver specific advertisements to you, which appear on pages throughout our websites. These companies collect non-identifiable information about your visits to our websites and other websites in order to provide advertisements about products and services that may be of interest to you. These companies may also aggregate your non-personal information for use in targeted advertising, marketing research, and other similar purposes. These companies may place their own cookies on your computer.

**IV. Security of the Information We Collect**

The security of your personal information is important to us. We maintain electronic and procedural safeguards to secure your personal information. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet, and there is always some risk in transmitting information electronically. 

The personal information we collect is stored within databases held by third party companies with excellent reputations as service providers.  They use security measures consistent with industry standards, such as firewalls and encryption technology, to protect your information. However, since no security system is impenetrable, they, and correspondingly we, cannot guarantee the security of our databases; nor can anyone guarantee that information you supply won’t be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. Of course, any personally identifying information you authorize us to post to TheNibble.com website, such as a Letter to the Editor with your name, city, and state, is available to anyone reading the website.

**V. Accuracy of the Information We Collect**

Any questions you may have regarding our Privacy Policy; the accuracy of your personal information; the use of your personal information; or any requests that we correct, update, or remove your information in our databases; should be directed via e-mail or regular mail addresses below.

After receiving a request to change your information, we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that all of your personal information stored in databases we actively use to operate our website will be updated, corrected, changed or deleted, as appropriate, as soon as reasonably practicable. However, we reserve the right to retain in our archival files any information we remove from or change in our active website databases. We may retain such information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our terms of use. In addition, it is not technologically possible to remove each and every record of the information you have provided to us. A copy of your personal information may exist in a non-erasable form that will be difficult or impossible for us to locate.

This Policy is effective as of February 1, 2005. We reserve the right to change this Policy at any time, and will post any changes to this Policy as soon as they go into effect. The date of the most recent revisions will appear at the top of this page as the Effective Date. You may wish to keep a copy of the Policy as of this reading and check back from time to time to see if a revision has been made.  However, continued access of TheNibble.com website by you will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy. 

If you have other concerns or questions about any aspect of this policy, please [click here](mailto:editors@thenibble.com) to e-mail us.* We welcome your feedback. You can also send us regular mail at the following address: 

Privacy Policy Coordinator  
THE NIBBLE  
15 West 72nd Street  
New York, NY 10023

*The direct address is editors -at - thenibble.com, substituting @ for -at. We use this convention to stop spam-harvesting spiders from harvesting our addresses and deluging us with spam.
